Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - F
        - Funkmaster Flex - 60 minutes of funk (Volume IV: the mixtape) (Disc one), 2000; SR-16009; Funkmaster Flex (Box 272)
          In same jacket as # SR-16010. Double album.
          Catalog # 501090; A-side Matrix # 50109010001A1
        - Funkmaster Flex - 60 minutes of funk (Volume IV: the mixtape) (Disc two), 2000; SR-16010; Funkmaster Flex (Box 272)
          In same jacket as # SR-16009. Double album.
          Catalog # 501090; A-side Matrix # 50109010001C1
        - Funkmaster Wizard Wiz - Put that head out, 1985; SR-16011; Funkmaster Wizard Wiz (Box 272)
          Catalog # TUF 120011; A-side Matrix # TUF 120011-A
        - Funky DL - Classic moves, 1996; SR-16012; Funky DL; Guile (Box 272)
          Catalog # ICE1041; A-side Matrix # ICE 1041 A-1-1-1
          DL Productions
        - Fabuloso, Nico - Watery nuts, 1992; SR-28962; Fabuloso, Nico (Box 273)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # NICO-A
          NI-TY Records
        - Fania All Stars - Live at Yankee Stadium (vol. 2), 1975; SR-28963; Fania All Stars (Box 273)
          In same jacket as # SR-28964. Different discs.
          Catalog # SLP 00477; A-side Matrix # SLP-00477-A
        - Fania All Stars - Live at Yankee Stadium (vol. 1), 1975; SR-28964; Fania All Stars (Box 273)
          In same jacket as # SR-28963. Different discs.
          Catalog # SLP 00476; A-side Matrix # SLP-00476-A
        - Fatback Band - Raising hell, 1975; SR-28965; Fatback Band (Box 273)
          Catalog # EV-6905; A-side Matrix # EV6905A-AD JR
        - F.B.Z.T. (Flatbush Zulu Troopers) - Thigh high thong, 2000; SR-28981; F.B.Z.T. (Flatbush Zulu Troopers) (Box 273)
          In same jacket as # SR-28982. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # PRM-2347; A-side Matrix # PRM 2347-A
          Planet Rock Music
          Bronx, New York
        - F.B.Z.T. (Flatbush Zulu Troopers) - Thigh high thong, 2000; SR-28982; F.B.Z.T. (Flatbush Zulu Troopers) (Box 273)
          In same jacket as # SR-28981. Multiple copies.
        - F.B.Z.T. (Flatbush Zulu Troopers) - Thigh high thong, 2000; SR-28983; F.B.Z.T. (Flatbush Zulu Troopers) (Box 273)
        - Featurecast - Music for fat kids EP, 2007; SR-17629; Featurecast (Box 273)
          Catalog # AFA-FW14; A-side Matrix # AFAFW-14-A
          Funk Weapons
        - Fela - Perambulator, 1983; SR-28966; Fela; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo; Egypt 80 (Box 402)
          Catalog # LIR 6; A-side Matrix # LIR 6A - FIS
          Lagos International Records
        - Fela - Army arrangement, 1985; SR-28967; Fela; Kuti, Fela Anikulapo (Box 402)
          Catalog # CELL 6109; A-side Matrix # CELL-6109-THAT
        - Ferrara - Wuthering Heights, 1979; SR-28968; Ferrara (Box 402)
          Catalog # MSI 008; A-side Matrix # MSI 008 AS-1A
        - Fever II - Funky pledge, 1982; SR-28969; Fever II (Box 402)
          Catalog # MG 101; A-side Matrix # SUN 221ARGH
          Moonglow
        - Fever II - Funky pledge, 1982; SR-28980; Fever II (Box 402)
        - Fiasco - Las mujeres (the women), 1994; SR-28984; Fiasco (Box 402)
          In same jacket as # SR-28985. Different discs.
          Catalog # SR12260; A-side Matrix # SR-12260-A
          Strictly Rhythm
        - Planet Soul - Set u free (the remixes), 1996; SR-28985; Planet Soul (Box 402)
          In same jacket as # SR-28984. Different discs.
          Catalog # SR12428; A-side Matrix # SR-12428-A
        - Final Edition - No limit; I can do it (anyway you want), 1979; SR-28986; Final Edition (Box 402)
          Catalog # VAR 19795; A-side Matrix # VAR-19795 A
          VAP Records, Inc.
          Amityville, New York
        - Flack, Roberta - Roberta Flack, 1978; SR-28987; Flack, Roberta (Box 402)
          Catalog # SD 19186; A-side Matrix # STA-784131-G
        - Floaters - Magic (We thank you), 1978; SR-28988; Floaters (Box 402)
          Catalog # DM-13; A-side Matrix # DM-13-A
        - Flock of Seagulls - I ran, 1982; SR-28989; Flock of Seagulls (Box 402)
          Catalog # JIVE T 14; A-side Matrix # JIVE T 14-A3
          London, England
        - Foxy - Party boys, 1979; SR-28990; Foxy (Box 402)
          Catalog # 30015; A-side Matrix # DA 30015-A AM (RE)
          Dash
        - Free Weel - Acid party, 1989; SR-28991; Free Weel (Box 402)
          Catalog # D.R. 142200; A-side Matrix # 521 A
          Downtown Records (Canada)
        - Fresh - Omniverse, 1978; SR-28992; Fresh (Box 402)
          Catalog # P7-10028R1; A-side Matrix # P7-10028RIA-13A
          Prodigal
        - Fullmoon - Spoonfull of soul; What you want me to do, 1994; SR-17630; Fullmoon; Soul S.K. (Box 402)
          Catalog # PA 50-39895; A-side Matrix # 5039895 A
          Public Attack
          Frankfurt, Germany
        - Fun City - Let's dance (baila), 1996; SR-28993; Fun City (Box 402)
          Catalog # CR-395; A-side Matrix # CR-395-A
        - Funkadelic - One nation under a groove, 1978; SR-28994; Funkadelic (Box 402)
          Catalog # WBSD 8803; A-side Matrix # WBSD 8803 WMI-1018 VIII-S SRI
        - Funkestra - Don't stop your love, 1982; SR-28995; Funkestra (Box 402)
          Catalog # MP 1201; A-side Matrix # MP-1201-A
          Metro Productions
          Stamford, Connecticut
        - Funky DL - Soul silhouette; It's about time (And that's true), 1996; SR-16013; Funky DL (Box 402)
          Catalog # 12 MST 003; A-side Matrix # 12 MST-003-A1
          Almost Records
        - Funky Four - Feel it (The Mexican), 1983; SR-16014; Funky Four; Funky 4 + 1 (Box 402)
          In same jacket as # SR-16014. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SH-463; A-side Matrix # VID-264-A
        - Funky Four - Feel it (The Mexican), 1983; SR-16015; Funky Four; Funky 4 + 2 (Box 402)
          In same jacket as # SR-16015. 2 copies.
        - Funky 4 Plus 1 - That's the joint, 1980; SR-16016; Funky 4 Plus 1; Funky 4 + 1 (Box 402)
          Catalog # SH-554; A-side Matrix # VID-186-A
        - Funky Four - Do you want to rock (Before I let go), 1982; SR-16017; Funky Four; Funky 4 + 2 (Box 402)
          Catalog # SH 586; A-side Matrix # SH-586-A
        - Funky People - Funky People, 1996; SR-16018; Funky People; Ware, Cassio (Box 402)
          Catalog # SLIP 50; A-side Matrix # SLIP 50-A1
          Slip 'n' Slide
        - Funky People - Funky People, 1995; SR-16019; Funky People; Ware, Cassio (Box 402)
          Catalog # FPR-1002; A-side Matrix # FPR-1002-A
          Funky People
        - Funn - School Daze, 1981; SR-16020; Funn (Box 402)
          Catalog # M-101-PRO; A-side Matrix # M-101A-PRO
          Magic Records
        - Funny - Fungi; Sweet fungi soca, 1980; SR-16021; Funny; Lord Funny (Box 402)
          Catalog # GS2717; A-side Matrix # GS 2717A
          Straker's Records
        - Funtopia - Beautiful people; Let us rise, 1989; SR-16022; Funtopia (Box 402)
          Catalog # WAR 041; A-side Matrix # WAR-041-A
          Idlers
        - Furious Five - Sun don't shine in the hood; Somebody else, 1994; SR-16023; Furious Five; Da Original (Box 402)
          Catalog # SBAB 78009-1; A-side Matrix # 72392-78009-1-SIDE 1
          Street Life Records
        - Furius Kay - Life's too short, 1999; SR-16024; Furius Kay; Valentino, Lou (Box 402)
          Catalog # FTONE050; A-side Matrix # DFI-9 9-3 FTONE 050 A
          Funky Tone
        - Futura 2000 - The escapades of Futura 2000, 1982; SR-16025; Futura 2000 (Box 402)
          Catalog # AZ/0 155; A-side Matrix # AZ 155 A
        - Futura 2000 - The escapades of Futura 2000, 1994; SR-16026; Futura 2000 (Box 402)
          Catalog # FUTURA 2000; A-side Matrix # FUTURA 2000 A
          360° Records
          Heidelberg, Germany
        - Future Forces - Imprint; Constant, 1997; SR-16027; Future Forces; Fierce (Box 402)
          Catalog # RH07; A-side Matrix # RH-07X1
          Renegade Hardware
        - Future Loop Foundation - Daddy radical, 1998; SR-16028; Future Loop Foundation (Box 402)
          Catalog # LIQ 016; A-side Matrix # LIQ 016 A-1-1-1
          Liquid
          Sheffield, United Kingdom
        - Future Loop Foundation - Karma; Remote viewing, 1997; SR-16029; Future Loop Foundation (Box 402)
          Catalog # BARK 032 T; A-side Matrix # BARK 032T A2
          Planet Dog
        - Future Sound of London - We have explosive, 1997; SR-16030; Future Sound of London (Box 402)
          Catalog # ASW 6196; A-side Matrix # ASW-6196-A
        - Futures - Past, present, and The Futures, 1978; SR-28996; Futures (Box 402)
          Catalog # JZ 35458; A-side Matrix # P.I.R. AL-35458-1B
        - Futuristic - Body talk, 1987; SR-16031; Futuristic (Box 402)
          Catalog # QS 005; A-side Matrix # QS-005-A
          Quazar Records
          Elmhurst, New York
        - Futuristic Soul - Old school "Jack"; The party, 1995; SR-16032; Futuristic Soul; Cisky (Box 402)
          In same jacket as # SR-16033. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DIG P3; A-side Matrix # DIG-P3-A
          Dig It International
        - Futuristic Soul - Old school "Jack"; The party, 1995; SR-16033; Futuristic Soul; Cisky (Box 402)
          In same jacket as # SR-16032. 2 copies.
        - Futuristic Soul - Old school "Jack"; The party, 1995; SR-16034; Futuristic Soul; Cisky (Box 402)
        - Fab 5 Freddy - Change the beat, 1982; SR-30938; Fab 5 Freddy; Be-Side (Box 147)
          Catalog # CEL 156; A-side Matrix # A-0156-Male